(Raj:)That's very mature of you.
(Sheldon:)Well, I've been on a little
trip myself recently.
(Sheldon:)Not to Sin City
but to Sincere City.
(Sheldon:)Where instead of genital warts,
the only growth
(Sheldon:)you'll come back with
is personal growth.
(Penny:)And there's your next T-shirt.
(Howard:)Ooh, check out
the stripper pole.
(Bernadette:)You know what that means.
(Leonard:)That Raj'll be on it before
we make it to the freeway?
You know it!
(whooping)
(Bernadette:)This is so cool.
Let's have champagne!
(Leonard:)Mm-hmm.
(Leonard:)Well, I would like
to propose a toast
(Leonard:)to a well-deserved weekend of...
Aha!
(all scream)
What are you doing?!
(Sheldon:)My plan was to jump out
at the state line,
(Sheldon:)but one of my nose plugs
fell into the toilet.
(Penny:)You couldn't give us
just one weekend?
(Stuart:)I told him
this was a bad idea.